# Ostap Maksymiv

 ♥ Rzeszów, Poland
 ☑ ostaperad@gmail.com

**4** +48 604 511 252

• ostapmaxportfolio.com

in ostap-maksymiv

♠ OstapMaksymiv

## About me

I am a third-year university student with commercial work experience. I handle tasks of any complexity with diligence, responsibility, and a focus on results. My background has equipped me with strong problem-solving and time-management skills.

## Education

# University of Information Technology and Management(UITM)

Oct 2022- Present

BS in Information Technology

o GPA: 4.0

# Experience

Game Developer

Rzeszów, Poland May 2024 - Jul 2024

Simplicity Games

Game Development. Creation and optimization of gameplay mechanics

- o Debugged and optimized existing game code to improve performance and stability.
- Developed and implemented new game features in Unity using C#.
- Collaborated with designers and developers to refine the mechanics of the game.
- o Conducted testing and troubleshooting to ensure a smooth user experience.
- Assisted in UI/UX improvements for better gameplay flow.

#### Stack:

- C#, Unity Game development and scripting
- Unity UI, Animator UI implementation and animations
- Git, GitHub Version control and collaboration
- Game Physics & Optimization Performance tuning and bug fixing
- Agile (Scrum) Team collaboration, sprint planning, and retrospectives

# App Developer

Rzeszów, Poland (Remote) Jun 2023 - Aug 2023

2SI -  $Sieciowe\ Systemy\ Informatyczne$ 

o Developed backend features using Python and MongoDB.

- Created and optimized RESTful APIs.
- Debugged and improved existing code.
- Worked in an Agile team with code reviews and stand-ups. and Perl scripts

## **Projects**

# Roomzee (Platform for booking and managing accommodations)

## GitHub Repository

- User-friendly interface: Simple and easy-to-navigate design for an enhanced user experience.
- Real-time availability: Instantly check the availability of accommodations.
- Personalized recommendations: Get tailored accommodation suggestions based on preferences.
- Integrated chat: Communicate directly with hosts for quick responses and seamless bookings.
- o Modern web technologies: Built with the latest tools to ensure speed, reliability, and performance.

Used: React, GSAP (for animations), Node.js, Express, MongoDB, WebSockets, SCSS, AXIOS, Zustand ,bcrypt, cookie-parser, cors, jsonwebtoken, nodemon, prisma

## RabbitHole (Messenger to deep conversations and AI-driven analysis.)

GitHub Repository

- o This project was built using Node.js and MongoDB.
- The application allows users to exchange messages both between themselves and with AI.
- It integrates the Gemini model (for basic chats) and Hume AI (for emotion analysis and generating responses).

Used: Node.js, Express.js, MongoDB, Mongoose, JWT, Tailwind CSS, Gemini and Hume AI – AI models for analyzing and generating responses

# Euphoria and Game Lobby Project (Two projects)

First GitHub Repository 🗹 Second GitHub Repository 🗹

#### First Project

- User Authentication: Secure user authentication with JWT and bcrypt.
- o Image Uploads: Image uploads handled with Multer and stored on AWS S3.
- o Dynamic Content Rendering: EJS templates for dynamic content rendering.
- Session Management: Session management with express-session and connect-mongo.
- o Responsive Design: Responsive design with Swiper and animate.css.
- o Database: MongoDB for data storage, accessed via Mongoose.

## Second Project

- Tic-Tac-Toe: A classic game where players take turns marking spaces in a 3x3 grid, aiming to align three
  of their marks in a row.
- Snake: A timeless game where players control a snake to eat food, causing it to grow longer while avoiding collisions with the walls and the snake's own body.
- o Game Lobby: A centralized interface from which users can choose to start either of the games.

The Second project is a mobile game that my team, including Taras Dushenko, Mateusz Cisło and me, developed for our university. The project is a Game Lobby with two games to choose from: Tic-Tac-Toe, which can be played both offline and online with a friend, and the classic Snake game, where you collect apples.

## Skills

Languages: English- B2, Polish- B2, Ukrainian- Native

Programming Languages: JavaScript, TypeScript, HTML, CSS, SASS, SCSS, Python

Libraries Frameworks: Node.js, React, Tailwind, Axios, jQuery, Express.js, Redux.js, Hume AI, Gimini AI

Database: MongoDB, FireBase, MySQL, PostgreSQL

Tools Platforms: Git, GitHub, Gitlab, Vercel, Figma, Docker, Webpack, Android Studio, Zustand